<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Red Flare</title>
    <description>We are a group of anti-fascist investigators, using open source and investigative methods to expose and oppose the far right in Britain.</description>
    <link>https://redflare.info</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:14:16 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:14:16 +0100</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>

    
    
    <item>
      <title>Neo-Nazis call for arson attacks on immigration-related charities</title>
      <description>A far-right Telegram group with 13,000 members is sharing a list of 39 immigration-related charities, advice centres and solicitors as targets for arson attacks on Wednesday night.</description>
      <link>https://redflare.info/articles/neo-nazi-arson-threat-immigration-solicitors/</link>
      <guid>https://redflare.info/articles/neo-nazi-arson-threat-immigration-solicitors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convicted neo-Nazi terrorist was at Southport riot</title>
      <description>One of the far-right activists who travelled to Southport on Tuesday night was Matthew Hankinson, an unrepentant neo-Nazi terrorist, who was jailed for six years for his membership of the proscribed neo-Nazi youth group National Action.</description>
      <link>https://redflare.info/articles/convicted-neo-nazi-terrorist-southport-riot/</link>
      <guid>https://redflare.info/articles/convicted-neo-nazi-terrorist-southport-riot/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report: Conservative-endorsed “youth” group Turning Point UK linked to political violence</title>
      <description>We infiltrated Turning Point UK.</description>
      <link>https://redflare.info/articles/report-conservative-endorsed-youth-group-turning-point-uk/</link>
      <guid>https://redflare.info/articles/report-conservative-endorsed-youth-group-turning-point-uk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Hull Hitler” Forms Another New Far-Right Party</title>
      <description>Another split from Patriotic Alternative registers with the Electoral Commission</description>
      <link>https://redflare.info/articles/hull-hitler-forms-another-new-far-right-party/</link>
      <guid>https://redflare.info/articles/hull-hitler-forms-another-new-far-right-party/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Khan Protest to Take Place in Newham During Palestine March</title>
      <description>A protest against the London mayor has gone viral on social media.</description>
      <link>https://redflare.info/articles/anti-khan-protest-newham-palestine-march/</link>
      <guid>https://redflare.info/articles/anti-khan-protest-newham-palestine-march/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leading Patriotic Alternative Organiser Jailed for Two Years</title>
      <description>Patriotic Alternative (PA)’s Yorkshire regional organiser Samuel Melia, has been jailed for two years today.</description>
      <link>https://redflare.info/articles/leading-patriotic-alternative-organiser-sentence/</link>
      <guid>https://redflare.info/articles/leading-patriotic-alternative-organiser-sentence/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Close to Neo-Nazi Terrorism is the New Fascist Homeland Party?</title>
      <description>Despite Homeland’s efforts to distance themselves from PA’s more overt neo-Nazi politics, and their rejection of labels such as &apos;fascist&apos; or &apos;far-right&apos;, some of the fledgling party’s founding members have emerged from a neo-Nazi milieu</description>
      <link>https://redflare.info/articles/close-neo-nazi-terrorism-new-fascist-homeland-party/</link>
      <guid>https://redflare.info/articles/close-neo-nazi-terrorism-new-fascist-homeland-party/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Britain's Newest Fascist Party are Going Viral on TikTok</title>
      <description>Homeland are reaching tens of thousands of people through the social media platform</description>
      <link>https://redflare.info/articles/britains-new-fascist-party-are-going-viral-on-tiktok/</link>
      <guid>https://redflare.info/articles/britains-new-fascist-party-are-going-viral-on-tiktok/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Far-Right Intent on Violence Following Inflammatory Statements by Leading Politicians</title>
      <description>We have seen messages in which far-right activists discuss attacking pro-Palestinian protestors, anti-fascists and ethnic minorities.</description>
      <link>https://redflare.info/articles/meeting-points-far-right-saturday/</link>
      <guid>https://redflare.info/articles/meeting-points-far-right-saturday/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Organiser in Homeland Party had Three Shotguns Seized by Police</title>
      <description>Anthony Burrows recently lost an appeal to have his shotgun certificate reinstated.</description>
      <link>https://redflare.info/articles/key-organiser-in-homeland-party-has-three-shotguns-seized-by-police/</link>
      <guid>https://redflare.info/articles/key-organiser-in-homeland-party-has-three-shotguns-seized-by-police/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neo-Nazi Streamer and Patriotic Alternative activist “Yuro” Exposed as Stefan Rutland</title>
      <description>Red Flare can reveal the identity of “Yuro” - a founding host of the now-defunct, virulently racist neo-Nazi podcast, The Absolute State of Britain (TASOB), and a key figure in fascist party Patriotic Alternative (PA) - as Stefan Kelvin Rutland, originally from South London and now living in Anglesey, North Wales.</description>
      <link>https://redflare.info/articles/neo-nazi-yuro-stefan-rutland/</link>
      <guid>https://redflare.info/articles/neo-nazi-yuro-stefan-rutland/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neo-Nazi Homeland Party Fall Out With Cannock Anti-Migrant Protestors</title>
      <description>Following our exposés last week, the neo-Nazi Homeland Party have been asked to leave the anti-migrant campaign in Cannock, Staffordshire by local residents and the council candidate they had been supporting.</description>
      <link>https://redflare.info/articles/homeland-party-fall-out-cannock/</link>
      <guid>https://redflare.info/articles/homeland-party-fall-out-cannock/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
